情報
謡 bunu
優しい火だまりにチャイムがディレイする
方向を撫でる風
息吹は深くなってく
遠回りの涙 名前つけた明日
重なる未来のノーライン
See you next time.
I don't know why, but people are always apologizing to me.
I hear she was born with a strong sixth sense, so she draws spirits over to her.
Her name's even Sadako, like from the rain.
Her parents must have had foresight to give her such a perfect name, know what I mean?
I'm done. Go ahead.
I'm sorry to disappoint you all, but I can't actually see spirits or anything.
Also, my name is Sawako, not Sadako.
Sawako, and it's written as Cheerful Child.
For some reason, ever since I can remember, everyone has been afraid of me.
But all I want is to get along with them.
And I'm gonna try my best today, too.
Apparently, there's a ton of famous celebrities that visit there.
Hirano, Endo...
Hello there.
I think I've got my cheerful greeting down.
Morning.
Yo, you walked?
It's Kazuhaya.
Incredible.
He's always surrounded by people.
He's cheerful and positive, too.
Hey there, Kuro-Numa.
Ryo!
He talks to me the same way he talks to everyone else and treats me as Niko.
G-good.
Yo, Ryo.
Yo.
Ugh.
You do your homework, Kazuhaya?
Kazuhaya is the complete opposite of me.
It's like everyone gathers around Kazuhaya, and everything just flows from there.
The day of the high school entrance ceremony.
Um...
If you happen to be looking for Kitahorohai, it's that way.
Thanks a lot.
People usually apologize to me when I talk to them.
But he smiled and told me thank you.
From that day on, Kazehaya has become someone I admire.
And one day, I sincerely hope I can become a person like him.
Here's the plan. The day before the closing ceremony.
Let's do a test of courage.
Going?
If you plan on going, I'll have this pinned to the bulletin board,
so write your name on it. I hope everyone can go.
Everyone? But doesn't that mean...
You think Sadako's coming?
If she does, the real thing might show up.
I can't live up to their expectations.
If I went and nothing ended up appearing, would it disappoint them?
Now, once the closing ceremony ends, it's summer break.
And summer break means summer school.
So, who wants to come and help their teacher out?
I need one person to come before class over break.
It's not forever.
If nobody volunteers, I'll just choose.
I just want a break.
Everyone's stressed out.
Um...
If you're okay with me, then...
Oh, you sure? Thank you, Kuro Numa.
Hey, Teach.
Every single time these jobs come up, they fall on Kuro Numa.
No way.
It just doesn't seem fair to me, dumping all these random duties on her, you know?
Then, will you do it, Kazuhaya?
Huh?
Hmm...
Y-yeah.
I will.
He noticed it.
That I was doing all these jobs.
You must allow me to handle this.
It is summer, and I honestly don't have anything to do.
I've got time.
So much time.
I live nearby and I have so much free time.
If that's the case, Kuro Numa it is.
That was a close one.
What a relief.
He noticed it.
I thought I was invisible, but he knew.
He's such a nice person.
That makes me so happy.
Sarako!
Shina, hi!
It's been a while, huh?
It has.
I mean, we're in different classes now.
How's yours?
Is there anyone from our elementary or middle school?
No, but there's this boy.
His name is Kazuhaya and he's...
Ah!
That really cheerful guy?
He's not just really cheerful.
The guy's 100% cheerful.
Actually, it's like his entire existence is made out of pure cheer.
Ah!
Kazuhaya!
Oh my gosh!
He just heard everything you said!
Say you're sorry!
Ah!
Say sorry!
My compliment was taken as an insult?
Hey.
Tell me.
Just now.
What should I take that ass?
Ah!
Ah...
Okay, roger that.
Ah!
Wait a sec, I'm coming over there.
I never really had a chance to talk with you.
Ah!
Wait...
Isn't this amazing, Sadako?
Kazuhaya's the type of person that can't sit back and ignore the Outcast in class.
Well, my job's done, so see ya!
Kaze Haya, he's such a... such a wonderful person.
Once I explained my feelings, he understood.
He believed me. He didn't call me a liar.
I'm glad.
Honestly, I totally thought you hated me, Kuro Numa.
Hated? That's not true at all.
Actually, I've always wanted to become a cheerful person like you, Kaze Haya. I mean it.
Well, I don't know. I'm sure you're overestimating how cheerful a person I am.
I'm not, but it's true. Even your name is cheerful.
Okay, but what about you?
Sawako.
Sawako Kuro Numa, isn't it?
Yeah, but no one really calls me that.
I think that this might be the first time I've cleared up a misunderstanding.
Well, when we talked it out, you told me how you really felt.
So nice. This person is... so nice.
This is... the first time someone calls me by my real name.
What a feeling.
You should come to the test of courage too, Kuro Numa.
The first time in my whole life.
I'll do the test of courage, but I'll sign my name in secret.
What?
Sawako?
Yeah, for the test of courage, it'll be way more fun if someone plays the ghost role.
And if it's Sawako, just her standing there would make everyone pee their pants.
Excuse me.
When did you get here?
Um, about that role, I'd like to play it if that's alright.
Huh?
No, it's fine.
You shouldn't do it unwillingly.
Well, when we talked it out, you told me how you really felt.
I... haven't done anything unwillingly... ever.
I do want to get along better with everyone, but it's not like I'm trying to do it unwillingly for that or anything.
If I can do something, it makes me happy to help.
But at the same time, I can't live up to everyone's expectations.
I feel bad for saying this, but...
What?
The real thing won't appear.
Huh?
I don't have any psychic ability.
You don't?
Nope.
At all?
Yeah.
You're just now admitting this?
And did you just say everyone's expectations?
You're way off.
I can't believe that's what you've been thinking this whole time, right, Chizu?
But what the hell are you crying for?
I can't take out here she is.
I'm a real selfie for this time.
You're totally off the mark, too.
We're counting on you to be our ghost, then, Sarako.
Don't worry, we'll keep it a secret between just us.
So scare them to your heart's content.
Thank you.
I can't believe they understood how I really felt.
It may just be a small step, but I feel like I've changed.
Thank you so much.
I owe it all to you, Kasehaya.
A group will head out every ten minutes!
Looks like almost everyone's made it.
Sadako's the only one missing.
Huh?
Well, Sadako...
We said we'd keep it a secret!
Uh...
I want everyone to have fun, so I'll do my best.
So, so dark.
It's kind of spooky.
Those screams are pretty intense.
What do you think is happening in there?
Good job.
I'm so happy.
I managed to help everyone out this much.
Maybe I'll try biting a strand of hair next time.
Kurunuma?
Kasehaya!
What are you doing, huh?
I was playing the role of the spirit.
Oh, jeez.
Could have told me.
I did organize this entire thing, after all.
I thought you weren't coming.
If I did, it would take the chills away from you and wouldn't be as fun.
Chills?
What does that mean?
You're out here alone.
Aren't you scared?
No, I actually kind of like it out here at night.
Especially during the summer.
Like the air.
The smell.
The sound of the leaves.
And the bugs chirping, too.
I get it.
It feels kind of nice out here.
So you mind if I chill with you?
But, um, the test of courage.
Thanks to someone not showing up,
the number of people ended up odd.
So I got left out.
Scary, right?
What's happening right now?
Sarako!
Yano!
And Yoshida!
Hey, why is Kaze Haya here?
If the two of you knew about all this,
you should have told me.
Being good to her.
I'm cheerful, boys, or something else.
I seriously hate you guys.
Sarako?
Nice.
You were a real spookmaster.
Here, drink up.
Wow, thank you.
Such great people.
Look at you.
You're getting along with them.
Huh?
That's great.
Getting along with them?
I was.
It's...
It's all thanks to you, Kaze Haya.
Huh?
But I didn't do anything.
Yes, you did.
Kaze Haya,
you're the reason I was able to tell those two how I really felt.
I'm so glad I got to play the role of the ghost.
Know what, Kuro Numa?
You're actually really cheering.
And your attitude's so positive.
Cheery?
Me?
No one's told me that before.
Not in my entire life.
Stop staring.
I'm so sorry.
I let myself get carried away.
I promise I'll be extra careful.
Our eyes don't meet for over three seconds.
But I actually can't give you any bad luck so...
That isn't it.
That's embarrassing.
Don't make me say it.
He stopped talking all of a sudden.
So, I don't know what I'm supposed to do anymore.
My heart's going crazy.
So many feelings I've never felt before.
It's almost like I've been reincarnated.
It seems like Kasehaya keeps giving me a lot of these firsts.
I'm truly grateful I got the chance to meet him.
We made it!
It's summer break!
Before we leave, I'll announce a test of courage results.
First things first, man.
You gotta accept your punishment.
You never managed to reach the goal.
Guess you found me out.
First place is Tonika.
The prize is 60 scrubbing brushes.
What am I supposed to do with that?
And next, the punishment for Kasehaya's last place is...
Wait for it!
For a whole entire week, you get to be Sanako's boyfriend!
What did he just say?
Kasehaya, so I heard you were together with Sanako last night.
Was she making a move on you?
Just get together already.
You guys are taking this way too far.
Yeah, no way.
I'll do anything but that.
Hey, that's kinda...
Calling that a punishment's just insanely rude.
Kuro Numa, she's a person.
It's not funny.
Don't take that crap to heart.
Promise?
No.
You shouldn't defend me.
Kasehaya, your reputation...
You're gonna ruin it.
You've got it all wrong.
Well, not all of it.
It is true I was with Kasehaya yesterday.
But it...
It wasn't...
It really wasn't anything special, honestly.
It's just that...
Kasehaya is the type of person who treats everyone the same way.
I've got this.
It'll be okay.
I know how to clear up misunderstandings now.
That being said,
me being drawn to Kasehaya's kindness,
cheerfulness,
overwhelming positivity and honesty,
that's 100% fact.
So that part...
was not a misunderstanding.
Excuse me.
I'm sure I did the right thing.
That the misunderstanding was cleared up.
Since nothing I said was a lie,
every word of it was pure truth.
I'm sure I protected Kasehaya's reputation.
I'm sure I did the right thing.
What?
Even though it's summer break?
Mm-hmm.
I promised to go help my teacher.
Yes.
I...
do believe I did the right thing.
Really.
But...
it sure does feel lonely.
One summer break is over.
I'm just so afraid that...
he...
he never looked me in the eyes ever again.
He may start avoiding me.
After all this time,
I thought I was used to it.
But...
the way he treated me
made me so happy
that I'd forgotten...
how my world felt
before I met Kasehaya.
He's making everything new.
Why?
It's summer break, so...
now what?
Here.
For the night's reel, MVP.
Everyone apologized.
I understood then.
It's cleared up.
Thank you
for defending me
and for going out of your way
to bring this here.
And you're still talking to me.
Thank you.
You know...
after hearing that,
I don't think you really
understand me that well.
Don't worry about me.
But I do know
how you feel, Kasehaya.
You don't!
It's...
okay to get my hopes up, right?
About being able to see you
over summer break?
Back then?
Uh...
Um...
If you happen to be looking
for Kithohorohai,
it's that way.
Thanks a lot!
Mm-hmm.
The feeling that came over me
at that moment...
Which has only continued
to grow and grow since then...
Someday...
Will it reach from me to you?
Thank you.
Oh, no.
Stop it empty.
They are ready and theyيلated by the day-long process.
You did?
Oh, no.
No, no.
The answer will be nothing.
シャボン玉飛ばそう
空まではきっと届かない
家に壊れそう
未だら知りたいの永遠じゃない
このままずっと見えていたいけど
その空いっぱいの神飛行機
ほらいにね
ひとつだけ見つけて
次回 シーティングチェンジ
気づきはいつど
はないね
Teresa
ゆおめん